RESUME

SAMALA HARISH

S/O.VENKATESWARLU

E-mail: achieversathari@gmail.com

Phone no: +91 9014856640

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To obtain a challenging and responsible position in a professionally managed organization. Has an insight and analysis of organizational improvement that can be driven to the betterment of the company. Having strong Quantitative and Analytical skills. I would like to establish myself in a job that offers satisfaction through continuous knowledge acquisition and where achievement gets its due reward.

SUMMARY

Performance driven, Caring and enthusiastic teacher with a strong commitment to student development and the learning experience. Excellent background and proven success in helping students reach their full potential. Easily interacts with students and staff. Presents information in a wide variety of ways, emphasizing the relevance of classroom material to the world outside the classroom, with additional capabilities in.

Academic Qualifications

Completed **B.TECH(EEE)** from VAAGDEVI ENGINEERING COLLEGE, WARANGAL affiliated to JNTU ,HYD during the year 2009-2013 with an aggregate of 74%

Intermediate (M.P.C) at SVS Junior College, HANAMKONDA, in the year 2007-2009 with 92% Completed 10th class (S.S.C) in 2007 at SVV High School, KESAMUDRAM with 85%

Professional Experience

Working as a **Placement APTITUDE TRAINER** in MARRI LAXMAN REDDY INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (**MLRIT Engineering college**) (**DEC 2019 onwards**)

i)Taking CRT Aptitude classes to the different stream of students and each **Batch Size** containing minimum **60 students to Maximum 100 students**

ii)Conducting offline and online tests and also explaining test questions to help the students in enhancing their knowledge for in depth Content development

iii)Contributing for the **Development of Aptitude Material** for the students MLRIT and also **Conducting Mock Drives** for the students and also **Participating in the Actual Drives** as a Representative Member from the MLRIT

Working as a Part Timer QUANT FACULTY in THE PRINCETON REVIEW (May 2018 onwards)

i)Taking GRE, GMAT and SAT Quant(including Subject tests) and PSAT premium home tutoring

ii)Conducting **REFRESHER Sessions** to help the students in enhancing their knowledge for in depth Content development

iii)Contribution for Marketing: Giving a brief Orientation about the Products delivered by the organization.

Worked as a Quant Faculty at **Score Plus Academy at Mumbai.(August-2017-April-2018)** Key Roles:

- i)Taking GRE, GMAT and SAT Quant(including Subject tests) and ACT both in **ONLINE OFFLINE** Modes
- ii) Taking institutional Batches for SAT and ACT at Singapore International School(SIS), Mumbai.
- iii)Conducting Workshops to help the students in enhancing their knowledge

Worked as a **QUANT FACULTY in MANHATTAN REVIEW** since September 2015 to August 2017. Key Roles:

i)Taking GRE, GMAT, SAT and PSAT

ii)Conducting Workshops to help the students in enhancing their knowledge for in depth Content development

iii)Conducting strategy sessions for the products GRE, GMAT and SAT.

Worked as a QUANT FACULTY in THE PRINCETON REVIEW for 1year (2014-2015)

Key Roles:

i)Taking GRE, GMAT and SAT(including Subject tests),PSAT.

ii)Conducting WorkShops and Refresher sessions to help the students in enhancing their knowledge for in depth Content development

iii)Contribution for Marketing: Giving a brief Orientation about the Products delivered by the organization and conducting seminars in Institutions regarding prep courses thus helping the Company to generate Revenues.

iv)Utilized Corporate learning techniques and provided individual interaction to meet the needs of students with diverse learning styles.

Worked as a **high school math faculty in SRUJANA HIGH SCHOOL**, **UPPAL** for 1 year(2013-2014). Key Roles:

i)Maintain Complete responsibility for the organization in the department of IIT, NTSE

ii)Teaching for the High School Standard, helping students in Projects of self contained high school classrooms.

Computer Skills

Ms-office

Personal Profile

Name: SAMALA HARISH

Father's Name: VENKATESWARLU

D.O.B: 23/06/1992 Marital status: Married

Languages Known: Telugu, English, Hindi

Hobbies: Solving math problems, playing and watching cricket

Address For Communication:

14-31, Plot no.31, Street no 1, Sai Nagar Colony, 2nd left from the Sai Baba Temple, Chowdariguda,

Narapally

Mandal:Ghatkesar

Dist:Medchal Malkajgiri,TELANGANA. Pin: 500088

Declaration

I hereby declare that the information furnished above is correct to the best of my knowledge.

PLACE:

DATE:

(S.HARISH)